[{"answer": "Chanel Number Five. That always reminds me of home", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'm home now", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What are you doing", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Come on! Mom said you were sick. You're never happy to see me", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Just a little. I've had a tough day", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Grounded? Ha! The story of my life. I don't wanna go to my room. I wanna import Japanese cars. I wanna go to that place and discover the Beatles", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "She's not wasting any time. my friend and Mr. Square Root", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, a book... Excuse me for a second.", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What would you like", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yes. Who are you", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yeah. I'm surprised. It's really old...  Travels well though.  You know, the world looks a lot better from up here", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What are you shooting for", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No offense, but for a person who says she's lived an extra lifetime, you certainly are thick. Money is power.. Money makes people respect you..", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'm curious, but I don't want to know. Jeez, I hope you haven't been telling people what's going to happen to them", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Because nothing else matters. That's the great thing about love. Every time we argue, every time something goes wrong, and I know that I'm not perfect either, things just work out better in the end. Cause you're my baby and I love you", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Don't be cruel to a heart that's true", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "This morning was good", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I, that what all that nonsense was about this morning? You're worried about my business", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "But when my friend's elected President, men'1l stop wearing hats", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " He'll win", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh boy. my friend, what are microchips", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What will they be made of", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " For everyone", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "that place? I thought you'd be going to that place or that place. What's in that place", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I was at my friend's last night. You were terrific", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What were You doing there? You never told me you were singing with an R and B group", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "That's real big of you", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You're kidding. You wrote a song? Is it about a guilty girl and a trusting guy... she wants to hurt him, and he wonders why", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Fat chance. You know, my friend came to hear me last night. He told me to forget it. You told me to forget it. My parents tell me to forget it", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "If you took the trouble to write it, then sure, I'll take a look at it. But I'm beginning to think that maybe there's more to life than music. I wonder if people would still like me if I stopped being Mr. Excitement", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Don't be silly, I'm the best in the county", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I spend three hours a day practicing. I have trainers, I know what I'm doing", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I've got to go now", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I'll love you, too, my friend. I'll love you for twenty years", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh, God, my friend", "docId": "Peggy-Sue-Got-Married.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I'll never give up", "qsentId": 36}]